[
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Andantino stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Slow Speed",
      "Same Speed",
      "Fast Speed"
    ],
    "correct": "Medium Speed"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Grave stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Fast, Lively",
      "Very Slow, Lively",
      "Very Fast, Solemn"
    ],
    "correct": "Very Slow, Solemn"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Larghetto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Rather Lively",
      "Stop Completely",
      "Rather Fast"
    ],
    "correct": "Rather Slow"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Largo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Fast",
      "Same Speed",
      "Fast"
    ],
    "correct": "Slow"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Presto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Slow",
      "Same Speed",
      "Moderate Speed"
    ],
    "correct": "Fast"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Fortepiano stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Quiet",
      "Very Loud",
      "Quiet then immediately loud"
    ],
    "correct": "Loud then immediately quiet"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Sforzando stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Quiet",
      "Lively",
      "Quiet accented note"
    ],
    "correct": "Loud accented note"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Sforzato stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Quiet",
      "Lively",
      "Quiet accented note"
    ],
    "correct": "Loud accented note"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does A stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "To the / At the / In the manner of",
      "One / Two / Three / Four / Five",
      "Left / Right / Up / Down / Out"
    ],
    "correct": "To / At / In / By / For"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Alla stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "To / At / In / By / For",
      "One / Two / Three / Four / Five",
      "Left / Right / Up / Down / Out"
    ],
    "correct": "To the / At the / In the manner of"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Allargando stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Large",
      "Short",
      "Close"
    ],
    "correct": "Broadening"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Assai stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Large",
      "Short",
      "None"
    ],
    "correct": "Very"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Con stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Broadening",
      "Short",
      "Very"
    ],
    "correct": "With"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Col stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Broadening",
      "Short",
      "Very"
    ],
    "correct": "With"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Dolce stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Double",
      "Loud / Hard",
      "Angrily / Harsh"
    ],
    "correct": "Sweet / Soft"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does E stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Close",
      "Very",
      "With"
    ],
    "correct": "And"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Ed stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Close",
      "Very",
      "With"
    ],
    "correct": "And"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Espressivo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Graceful",
      "Very",
      "Explosive"
    ],
    "correct": "Expressive"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Giocoso stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Quick / Intense",
      "Quiet / Melancholic",
      "Solemn / Sad / Blunt"
    ],
    "correct": "Playful / Merry / Humourous"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Grazioso stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Grande",
      "Expressive",
      "Explosive"
    ],
    "correct": "Graceful"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Ma stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "To",
      "And",
      "Very"
    ],
    "correct": "But"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Maestoso stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Melodic",
      "Melancholic",
      "Melodramatic"
    ],
    "correct": "Majestic"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Meno stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Odd",
      "Even",
      "More"
    ],
    "correct": "Less"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Molto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "More / Large",
      "Less / Small",
      "Very / Little"
    ],
    "correct": "Very / Much"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Mosso stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Melodramatic",
      "Majestic",
      "Melodic"
    ],
    "correct": "Movement"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Moto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Melodramatic",
      "Majestic",
      "Melancholic"
    ],
    "correct": "Movement"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Senza stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "But",
      "And",
      "With"
    ],
    "correct": "Without"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Simile stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Merry",
      "Playful",
      "In a different way"
    ],
    "correct": "In the same way"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Troppo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "But",
      "Without",
      "Too Little"
    ],
    "correct": "Too Much"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Sostenuto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Detached",
      "Short",
      "Dull"
    ],
    "correct": "Sustained"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Tenuto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Not Sustained",
      "Sustained for double the note value",
      "Sustained for half the note value"
    ],
    "correct": "Sustained for the full note value"
  },
  {
    "grade": 2,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "How do you draw Tenuto?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Shown with a > above or below the note head",
      "Shown with a triangle above or below the note head",
      "Shown with a dot above or below the note head"
    ],
    "correct": "Shown with a horizontal line above or below the note head"
  }
]
